Finding Aid for Richard P. Miller papers, 1970-1979
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Richard P. Miller papers 1970-1979
Miller, Richard P.
3 linear feet
8921 Aa 2
Editor and publisher of the Daily Tribune; scrapbooks of newspaper columns and editorials.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Richard P. Miller (donor no. 5168 ) and came to the library in 1979.
The collection is open to research.
Richard P. Miller was editor and publisher of the Daily Tribune, a south Oakland County, Michigan, newspaper. He succeeded his father Philip F. Miller who died in 1970.
The collection consists mainly of clippings of his column "Personally Speaking" and the editorials that he wrote for the newspaper. There is also a small folder of biographical material.
Subjects:
American newspapers--Michigan--Oakland County.; Daily tribune (Royal Oak, Mich.); Journalists--Michigan--Royal Oak.; Oakland County (Mich.)
- Biographical material
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Newspaper column, "Personally Speaking"
  - 1970 (Box 1)
  - 1971 (Box 1)
  - 1972 (Box 1)
  - 1973 (Box 1)
  - 1974 (Box 1)
  - 1975 (Box 1)
  - 1976 (Box 1)
  - 1977 (Box 1)
  - 1978 (Box 1)
  - 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1970 (Box 2)
  - 1971 (Box 2)
  - 1972 (Box 2)
  - 1973 (Box 2)
  - 1974 (Box 2)
  - 1975 (Box 3)
  - 1976 (Box 3)
  - 1977 (Box 3)
  - 1978 (Box 3)
  - 1979 (Box 3)
Related Material
The library also houses the papers of his grandfather Floyd J. Miller and his father Philip F. Miller.